zst I'm from the city of Khmelnitsky You're from
зст Я из города Хмельницкий Вы откуда
Khmelnitsky interesting name I'm from the
хмельницкие интересное название Я из
city of
города
St. Petersburg interesting name you
санкт-петербург интересное название вам
like it somewhere in the Leningrad
нравится это где-то в Ленинградской
region yes Yes everything is absolutely correct Why did
области да Да всё верно соверше Почему у
we have the owl city hero city
нас же было сове горо город герой
Leningrad why was it renamed to
Ленинград зачем его переименовали в
some kind of
какой-то
St.  -Petersburg is also its old name, the
санкт-петербург этоже его ж старая назва
former Petrograd was well before that it
прежняя Петроград была ну до этого ещё
was still sa Well, why look, this is our
была са Ну так зачем Смотри это же наша
history
история
Leningrad that Nan Well, the hero city
Ленинград что Нан Ну город герой
Leningrad You heard that our grandfathers
Ленинград Вы слышали чтобы наши деды
For example, they had a hero city
Например у них было там город-герой
St. Petersburg there, yes that’s all  it’s clear,
санкт-петербург да это всё понятно Вы
tell me what channel you
скажите вы какой канал
run on YouTube What is the name of Andrey
ведёте ютубовские Как называется Андрей
Popik Andrey Popik
Попик Андрей Попик
Yes, that’s your name, my last name is popk
Да это так вас зовут фамилия у меня попк
Andrey It’s clear Ukrainians have such funny
Андрей Понятно украинцев такие забавные
surnames Popik, I had a friend, you have an
фамилии Попик у меня был друг у вас это
analogue of the Popov surname, I understood I had a
аналог Попов фамилия я понял У меня
friend who was familiar with  Ukraine since
товарищ был один знакомы с Украины с
Ivan Frankovsky he had the last name
Ивана франковского у него была фамилия
bruise bruise sailor there are some surnames that are
синяк синяк моряк такие вот фамилии есть
quite funny Ukrainians are more important to me than
достаточно забавные украинцев мне Поче
Funny bruise for example
чем Забавно синяк например
bruise Well they are more like
синяк Ну они больше похожи на на
nicknames like a nickname Well this is
прозвища как будто кличка Ну это в
basically understandable the Cossacks had
принципе объяснимо у казаков были
nicknames you and you  what is your
прозвища у вас да у вас у вас какой
surname what I don’t call my surname on
фамилия какая я не называю свою фами в
live broadcast especially what is the ending of the
прямом эфире тем боле концовка какая у
surname
фамилии
and in in
а ин
type there Savin Yes, for example, well,
ин типа там Савин Да например ну вот
this type Ilyin Ilyin let’s say Well in
такого типа Ильин Ильин допустим Ну ин
and im
и им
chi another friend I have from
чи ещё у одного товарища У меня с
Poltava I hope he has  everything is fine,
Полтавы есть Надеюсь у него всё хорошо у
his surname is drunk Yes Ponya And what does the surname
него фамилия пьяни Да Поня А что
Putin mean? She’s not Slavic. She’s not
Путин какая-то она не Славянская она не
Slavic. She’s some kind of Korela Vep Tae weighty Yes
Славянская она какая-то Корела веп Тае
weighty, well, something from there on
веская Да веская всё ну что-то оттуда с
the other side, there were a lot of
той стороны здесь же очень много было
Vepsians here, they assimilated the Slavs  it’s
вепсов они ассимилировать славяне их
easy to assimilate them, they all
просто ассимилировать они все
got mixed up, they didn’t just
перемешались не они просто по-русски
start speaking Russian the same way the Buryats now
начали говорить также как буряты сейчас
speak Russian in the majority Well, the judgment is
по-русски в большинстве говорят
not entirely correct, the judgment is not entirely correct,
Ну не совсем верно не совсем верно
then there were large migrations
суждение тогда же были большие миграции
and not from Russia there were no large
и не с Руси туда не было больших
migrations there were no  part of the Slavs
миграций были как не было часть славян
so in which Well, look, tell me in
так в каком Ну смотрите скажите мне в
what century
каком столетии
yes When there was a great migration of the Slavs
да Когда было великое переселение славян
to the north never in my life This did not happen
на север никогда в жизни Такого не было
at once it did
Это было не в одномоментно это не одно
not happen at one time at all And for many moments there
момент не было вообще И много момен там
500 years let’s say they gradually did not
500 лет допустим постепенно не
move to  there
переселялись они на
were a lot of them moving to the north
север переселялись их было очень много
No where did they come from they were moving
Нет откуда они откуда переселялись они
to these Klyazma all sorts of things from the side of
вот в эти Клязьмы всякие со стороны
Kievan Rus from the center from there there
Киевской Руси с центра вот оттуда там
was a conglomerate of large Slavs before
было конгломерат большой славян раньше
these were the lands of the Slavs then they began to
это были земли славян потом они начали
slowly crumble to crumble, that’s
потихоньку рассыпаться рассыпаться вот
exactly what it means, look, there’s a bunch of shorter
именно значит смотрите сидит куча короче
Slavs sitting in  Kievan Rus Yes, near the centers
славян в Киевской Руси Да возле центров
on fertile lands and is thinking about how
на плодородных землях и думает как бы
we can go somewhere north for these
нам попиздеть куда-то на север за эти
forests like in this mashkara, that’s exactly what they
леса типа в эту машкару вот они прямо
thought. All the peoples, on the contrary, like
так и думали Все народы наоборот типа
migrated here through the territory of
мигрировали сюда через территорию
Ukraine to Europe. Vikings used to
Украины в Европу Викинги раньше по всему
travel all over the world. Vikings  as before, before
миру ездили Викинги как раньше до
North America
Северной Америки
Dora, the Vikings the Vikings descended from
Дора так викинги викинги спускались с
north to south and not from the south, this is the
севера на юг а не с юга вот эта
territory where it
территория где она
was inhabited by the Slavs. Well, like from north to south
заселяли славян Ну типа с севера на юг
Miri, you know, there were Slavs and there were
Мири понимаешь славян было и там были
also there, just look at it, let’s do it if
там же раз воче смотри об давай так если
you have  look somewhere that some at
у тебя есть где-то глянуть что какой-то
least learned historian talks about the
хотя бы учёный историк рассказывает про
great migration of these Slavs over 500
великое переселение этих славян за 500
years, say I read before that, this is all
лет скажешь я почитаю до этого это всё
in short, your ideas are just okay, they didn’t
короче твои придумки просто ну окей Не
come, look, they came, what happened, I’ll
ве приезжали смотри приезжал что было я
tell you how it was, look,
тебе расскажу как было смотри приезжал
the governor came, he came  the prince and his retinue,
приезжал наместник князя с дружиной да
that is, they collected money like they
то есть они собирали бабки как
sent a governor from Moscow, for example,
губернатора присылают из Москвы например
now they sent a governor there to Buryatia. Yes,
сейчас там в бурятию прислали
this does not mean that
губернатора Да это не значит что в
a bunch of Russians came to Buryatia, that’s all,
бурятию приехала куча русских вот и всё
wait, friend, stand there, look. Come on,
подожди друг стоять смотри Давай ты мне
now you can also send me a link to the historian
сейчас тоже ссылку скинешь на историка
who is everything to me  it will tell and then you
который мне всё это расскажет а потом ты
will tell everything until that moment
будешь всё рассказывать до того момента
I don’t believe in it These are just words this is the
я в это не верю Это просто слова это
official history Yes, the prince prince
официальная история Да князь князь
reigned your official history Yes
княжил твоя официальная история твоя Да
no official take a Russian
нет официальная возьми российский
textbook Read the Russian teaching there that
учебник Прочитай российский уче там тот
Prince began to reign there and so on he
Князь начал княжить там и так дальше сам
read  read russian to the author who is the author
читал читал россий к автор кто автор
perper
перпер
dülfer
дюльфер
dülger because you have faith in you No you are a
дюльгер потому что тебе тебе веры Нет ты
very dangerous person
очень опасный человек
yes you will [ __ ]
да ты же наебёшь
you [ __ ] you How [ __ ] two fingers
тебе наебать Как [__] два пальца
piss perpen dülmen
обоссать перпен дюльмен
per perdy Yes [ __ ] what is this probably a
пер пердю Да бля что это навер
Ukrainian surname after all he is just a
украинская всё-таки фамилия он просто
native of Ukraine Pri  In the Soviet Union,
выходец из Украины При Советском Союзе
only Ukrainians have such surnames
го только у украинцев такие фамилии
Perper
перпер
Duke nothing
Дюка ничего не
was found Professor of
нашлось профессор
Moscow State University Professor of Moscow State University You have Alice, you
МГУ профессор МГУ с у тебя Алиса есть
can ask Alice I don’t have Alice I do
можешь спросить у Алисы У меня нет Алисы
n’t use it Well, I don’t know I don’t
я не польз а что Ну не знаю я не
use
пользуюсь у меня
Siri [ __ ] me Alice Come
Сири нахуй у меня Алиса Давай
on  Ivanka Who
се Иванка Кто
wrote the modern Russian
написал современный российский
history textbook Ivanka Who wrote the Russian
истории Иванка Кто написал российский
history textbook Russian
учебник по истории российский
and written by Moscow State University professor Ivan Trofimovich
и написал профессор МГУ Иван трофимович
fart And
пердю А
fart fart you are wrong, you
пердю пердю ты неправильно ты меня
misinformed me Yulka is like, well, that’s all
дезинформировали Юлька типа ну это всё
he’s not, maybe
он не это може итальянец
some Italian And you’ve already appropriated it to
какой-то А ты уже присвоил его
Ukraine  private yourself
Украин привате себ
right away and how quickly it turns out
сходу ви как быст выясняется
fart [ __ ]
пердю
We also say that, that’s why
Ебануться Мы тоже так говорим мы поэтому
we re-fart VG Well, in short, I never
мы пере пердю ВГ Ну короче я так и не
found it Well, God bless him, no, no, don’t let me Yes, I don’t, no,
нашёл Ну ладно Бог с ним не-не не давай
[ __ ], I enter it, it doesn’t work out,
Да я не не [__] я ввожу не получается
perr, and fart  that is, she’s
пер перр пе и пердю то есть она вот
just yes, I thought that the pen is why not
просто да я думал что пер поэтому не
Find pe iper Yulka Ir perd iper pe
Находи пе ипер Юлька Ир перд ипер пе
iper it was probably Italian or
ипер это наверное итальянское или
French something Yes,
французское что-то
anyway, I’m catching fish You
было Да всё равно вот у меня рыбку ловит
see, spell it, read how you
Видишь по буквам прочитай как ты
typed Paper
набрал Пейпер
Yulka
Юлька
Yulko dl not  ka a ko
юлько дль не ка а
[ __ ] You're typing it in one word
ко бля Ты одним словом это набираешь да
yes it's a few words it's us from him m
это что несколько сло это мы с него м
peredka
передка
an
ан
yulko yulko is a name And peper is a
юлько юлько - это имя А пепер - это
surname or a Jew or an Italian
фамилия или еврей или итальянец
I'd just like we'll stem from him fart perdy
бы я просто мы стем с него пердю пердю
wrote like
написал типа
this iper space
этот ипер пробел
yulko  or Croatian, he was someone there
юлько или хорват он кто-то там
Well, yes,
был Ну
Peper North [ __ ] Yes, they
Да пепер Север
don’t find some kind of hat on me
[__] Да не находят вот у меня какую-то
like you wrote Now I’m still
шляпку как ты написал Сейчас я ещё
Paper dash yulko like you m be Dash
Пейпер тире юлько как ты м бе Тире
space not dash I didn’t say those space is the
пробел не тире Я не сказал те пробел это
name and  surname separately I understand, it means I
имя и фамилия отдельно Я понял значит я
entered incorrectly, well, not a damn thing has changed,
вступил ну ни хрена особо не поменяло
everything is the same.
всё тоже само
I got the same thing. Oh,
Мне тоже самое
[ __ ], some kind of service I
выдало Ой [__] какой-то пер сервис Мне
got it, look at Google. This is Google, I don’t
выдало смотри Google Это это Google я не
know, maybe you find it in Yandex,
знаю может ты в Яндексе
you use Yandex, No, this
находишь ты Яндексом пользуешься Нет это
is Ivanka  voice assistant Yes, this is from
это Иванка голосовой помощник Да это с
plagiarism or from Alice
плагиате или с Алисы
Sir
Sir
Siri Yes, what a horror in
Сири Да ужас какой
short, the professor of Moscow State University should write down the
короче профессор МГУ надо записать
professor of
профессор
Moscow State University, they don’t find it Oh well, God bless him, I’d
МГУ не не находят Да ладно Бог с ним я
better look for your channel now, suddenly you
лучше сейчас твой канал поищу вдруг ты
deceived me here too,
меня и здесь обманул
look
смотри
Ivanka, what did the professor write, this [ __ ] is like
Иванка что писал профессор этот бляд как
him  Well, who wrote this book
он ну который этот книжку написал
on Russian history? Yes, what did he write about the
российскую по истории Да что писал о
resettlement of the Slavs to the north, whether or
переселении славян на север было или не
not the resettlement of the Slavs from Kievan Rus
было переселение славян с Киевской Руси
to the swamp did not happen, who the [ __ ]
на болото не происходило кому нахрен
needed to live in this shitty
нужно было жить в этой мухо
place in
срань в
2022? Defended a
2022 году Защитила ТП этой теме
doctoral dissertation on this topic by a professor at Moscow State University.
докторскую диссертацию профессора МГУ пи
Duke's puree
пюр
I understood everything It was very cool You are
Дюка я всё понял Это было очень круто Ты
beautiful subscribe to my Telegram right
красав подпишись на мий Telegram прямо
now the axis of wine and Pok
зараз ось вин а Пок
is more and more respectful YouTube taking us
це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня нас
through the ORV srg to your ban and a lot of
через срг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже багато
video I don’t show people at all times I don’t show
вдео не показую людям вчасно не показуе
information about streams For Tom  Togo shob
информация про стрими Тому для того щоб
mi Mali operative link write
ми Мали оперативный звязок пишиться
directly at the same time and while there in telegra okm
прямо зараз а пок там в телегра окм
video sche tezh va and korisna information and
видео ще теж ва и корисна информация и
we pon va tma on
мы пон ва тма по
operative link
оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in togo chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava Ukra
YouTube Слава Укра
subscribe
подпишись